In addition to keeping redundant backups of information,
you also have a redundant source of power to provide backup power.
So you have an uninterrupted power supply or UPS
transfer switches or transformers may also be involved and in
case the power is interrupted by weather or blackouts,
a backup generator is essential.
Often there will be two generators connected by two different transfer switches.
These generators might be powered by diesel or gasoline or
other fuel such as propane or even by solar panels,
a hospital or essential government agency might contract with more
than one power company and be on two different grids.
In case one goes out,
this is what we mean by redundancy.